Dorayall Christina Randolph

(702) 724-6465 dorayallcr@icloud.com

QUALIFICATIONS

Highly responsible and dependable individual who is positioned to excel as a member in a workplace.

SKILLS

- Bilingual
- Service oriented
- Detail oriented

EDUCATION

Basic Academy of International Studies, Henderson, NV Diploma

EXPERIENCE HIGHLIGHTS

Five Guys Burgers & Fries : Green Valley

All positions, July 8, 2020 - November 2020

 customer service, use of POS system, all food prep, grill, fry station consolidating, cleaning/daily duties, closing

Jimmy Johns: Henderson, NV

In-shop, June 6, 2019 - October 2019

 customer service, sandwich making, consolidating, use of POS system, prep for next shift, cleaning/daily duties

Shift Leader, October 2019 - November 2019

• helping out night crew, in charge of closing procedures, supervising, prep for next day shifts, counting out registers

Three Square, NV

Volunteer, December 28, 2018

Helped pack various produce and grocery items

 Communicated and worked with others in order to complete the given task -- part of personal project